question_data = [
{
"category": "History",
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Sargon II, a king of the Neo-Assyrian Empire, was a direct descendant of Sargon of Akkad.",
"correct_answer": "False",
"incorrect_answers": [
"True"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "The longest place named in the United States is Lake Chargoggagoggmanchauggagoggchaubunagungamaugg, located near Webster, MA.",
"correct_answer": "True",
"incorrect_answers": [
"False"
]
},
{
"category": "Science: Mathematics",
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "The binary number &quot;101001101&quot; is equivalent to the Decimal number &quot;334&quot;",
"correct_answer": "False",
"incorrect_answers": [
"True"
]
},
{
"category": "Science: Computers",
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "easy",
"question": "Linux was first created as an alternative to Windows XP.",
"correct_answer": "False",
"incorrect_answers": [
"True"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment: Film",
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "The movie &quot;Tron&quot; received an Oscar nomination for Best Visual Effects.",
"correct_answer": "False",
"incorrect_answers": [
"True"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment: Music",
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "The singer Billie Holiday was also known as &quot;Lady Day&quot;.",
"correct_answer": "True",
"incorrect_answers": [
"False"
]
},
{
"category": "General Knowledge",
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "The pickled gherkin was first added to hamburgers because a US health law required all fast-food to include a source of Vitamin C.",
"correct_answer": "False",
"incorrect_answers": [
"True"
]
},
{
"category": "Vehicles",
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "The term &quot;GTO&quot; was originated by Ferrari?",
"correct_answer": "True",
"incorrect_answers": [
"False"
]
},
{
"category": "General Knowledge",
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "easy",
"question": "Slovakia is a member of European Union-",
"correct_answer": "True",
"incorrect_answers": [
"False"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "easy",
"question": "There are 2 player roles in Trouble in Terrorist Town.",
"correct_answer": "False",
"incorrect_answers": [
"True"
]
}
]